Thomas C. O'Donnell Papers
Thomas Clay O'Donnell Papers
1900-1962
O'Donnell, Thomas C. (Thomas Clay), 1881-1962.
5.0 linear ft.
Papers of the American editor, author of books on upstate New York folklore and children's literature. Correspondence, incoming and outgoing (1900-1962); notebooks (1920-1957); scrapbooks; manuscript books, essays, lectures, plays, and poems, as well as research material; published articles, books, and plays; and memorabilia, including photographs. Correspondents include Conrad Aiken, C.W. Anderson, Richard Atwater, Marjorie Barrows, Henry Bedford-Jones, Maxwell Bodenheim, Padraic Colum, Albert B. Corey, Homer Croy, James W. Earp, Walter D. Edmonds, and Vincent Starrett.
149415
Biographical History
Thomas Clay O'Donnell (1881-1962) was an American magazine editor and author of books on upstate New York history and folklore.
Born on 29 July 1881 in a lumber camp near Saginaw, Michigan to George and Vesta O'Donnell, he received his early education in Vestaburg, Michigan, and later attended a business college in London, England, where he married another Michigander, Bertha May Smith, in 1905.
After returning to the United States, he lived from 1909-1919 in Battle Creek, Michigan where he taught at Battle Creek College before beginning his varied career as a magazine editor at Good Health, a magazine of the Battle Creek Sanitarium. Later he edited Cartoons magazine in Chicago. From 1923 to 1927 he was editor of The Writer's Digest in Cincinnati, where he also wrote and produced for radio station WLW, the Crosley Radio Corporation station there. An active Freemason for most of his life, he was for many years the editor of the monthly New York Masonic Outlook for the Grand Lodge of Masons of the State of New York. He edited the magazines Outing and Wayside Tales as well. From 1943 to 1945 he was production manager of Robert M. McBride & Company, publishers in New York City.
During his retirement, first in Boonville, New York, and then in Winter Park, Florida, O'Donnell wrote on the history of upstate New York. The publication in 1948 of The Sapbush Run: An Informal History of the Black River & Utica Railroad was followed by Snubbing Posts: An Informal History of the Black River Canal (1949) and Tip of the Hill: An Informal History of the Fairfield Academy and the Fairfield Medical College (1953). Of an intended trilogy on the history of the Black River, two books were completed: Birth of a River: An Informal History of the Headwaters of the Black River (1952) and The River Rolls On: A History of the Black River from Port Leyden to Carthage (1959).
His other works include several children's books, The Ladder of Rickety Rungs (1923) and The "Tell Me Again" Bible (1936), as well as plays for children and children's verse. Among his writings on the home are the books The Family Food (1911), A Garden for You (editor, 1946), and The Healthful House (1917, written with Lionel Robertson). O'Donnell wrote under numerous pseudonyms, including James Radley. He died at the Masonic Home in Utica, New York, on 11 November 1962, survived by his wife of 57 years and three children.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Thomas C. O'Donnell Papers comprise correspondence, memorabilia, notebooks, scrapbooks, writings in both manuscript and published form, and two small sections of biographical material and other writers' manuscripts. Principal items in the papers date from 1900 to 1962, with the years 1919 to 1955 most heavily represented.
Biographical material includes news clippings and other printed items about O'Donnell.
Correspondence dates from 1900 to 1962 and amounts to 556 letters, both incoming and outgoing. The earliest letters date from 1900 and are signed by "Clay" to his mother; the 37 family letters in these papers, mostly written by O'Donnell, extend to 1956. Besides 502 incoming letters from 1915 to 1962, there are 17 outgoing letters (mostly retained carbons) from 1915 to 1957.
Prominent among the correspondents are literary figures with whom he was associated, especially during the 1920s. Notable correspondents include Samuel Hopkins Adams (1), Conrad Aiken (7), C. W. Anderson (5), Richard Atwater (4),Marjorie Barrows (26), Henry Bedford-Jones (5), Ralph Bergengren (2), John Peale Bishop (1), Maxwell Bodenheim (5), Harold Brighouse (2), Abraham A. Brill (1), John Burroughs (1), Carl Carmer (1), Padraic Colum (4, including annotated typescript of the poem "Shall I Go Bound & You Go Free"), Albert B. Corey (19), Homer Croy (5), Jay Norwood ("Ding") Darling (3), John Drury (3), James W. Earp (13), Walter D. Edmonds (24), Edna Ferber (1), Richard Austin Freeman (2), John Merriman Gaus (2), Charles Dana Gibson (1), Arthur Edward Hamilton (14), Cassius Jackson Keyser (2), Alfred Kreymborg (2), George Barr McCutcheon (1), Thomas F. O'Donnell (1), Manuel Rosenberg (7), Vincent Starrett (10), and John Van Alstyne Weaver (2).
A name index and a topical index to the correspondenec are provided at the end of this inventory.
Manuscripts submitted to magazines edited by O'Donnell contains four items. The undated typescripts of the three Conrad Aiken poems "Clear Evening," "The Old House," and "Red Petals" were submitted to Cartoons, and Cassius Jackson Keyser (1862-1947), the Columbia University mathematician, contributed to Outlook the essay "How To Think Mathematically." Besides those manuscripts, there is in the correspondence section the annotated typescript of a Padraic Colum poem, "Shall I Go Bound and You Go Free," an enclosure in an undated letter of Colum.
Memorabilia includes advertisements and promotional brochures, photographs, and five folders of miscellanea. A group of eight caricature portraits includes several of O'Donnell, one of Padraic Colum that is inscribed with one of his poems, and four drawn by Manuel Rosenberg. Other photographs and caricatures will be found in the scrapbooks. There are three poems by Edwin Markham that are inscribed to O'Donnell, one of which, "Our Israfel," contains annotations in the poet's hand. Among the miscellanea are invitations, membership cards, other ephemera, and fragments.
The five Notebooks in Box 3 are undated, but contain material from the 1920s through 1957. Each of the four notebooks in small format contains diary fragments, clippings, quotations, and jottings; entries signed "Nicodemus" are O'Donnell's own. The first notebook is a commonplace book with lists of names and phrases. The second has on pages 58-87 and 90-91 a 1953 autobiographical sketch of his early years. The third contains sketches, dated 1927, for a children's book "The Road to Cuddledown," idea notes from 1946 to 1957, and the carbon of his letter of 9 January 1956 to Thomas F. O'Donnell. The fourth notebook, mostly from the 1950s, carries quotations and reminiscences. The largest notebook is a ring binder with notes on canals, apparently research material for the book Snubbing Posts.
Loose Scrapbook pages of general items, Masonic material, and clippings of O'Donnell's writings are arranged in boxes 3 and 4. Many of these pages carry his annotations. Seven folders of general material from 1910 to ca. 1953 contain clippings, cartoon sketches, and photographs. Another folder contains a Masonic scrapbook of programs and clippings. Approximately one hundred magazine articles, often written under pseudonyms, were clipped from magazines and mounted on pages that once constituted a scrapbook; arrangement of these printed articles is alphabetical by title for those from Cartoons, as is the arrangement of those from other magazines. Copies of published editorials and plays, also from the author's scrapbooks, complete the section.
Writings in manuscript contains manuscript version of both published and unpublished works. Many of these manuscripts carry notes of circa 1953 by the author. Of his books there are three folders of research notes and one folder of miscellaneous material for Birth of a River; the undated, unpublished typescript of A Jazz History of the United States, a whimsical account of some events in colonial American history; and the annotated typescript of a lengthy, unpublished autobiographical work (possibly with the working title"Aged in Wood") that centers on the lumber camp life of the author's childhood in northern Michigan. The typescripts of seventeen plays include a dramatic version of The Ladder of Rickety Rungs dated 1921. A complete file of the author's verses and poems -- published and unpublished -- are mostly typescript carbons, often annotated. An alphabetical list of all 250+ poems is available in the Manuscripts Division.
Writings, published include articles, books and plays, contributions to anthologies, Masonic writings in the Transactions of the American Lodge of Research of Free and Accepted Masons, and poetry. There is also a Masonic songster to which he contributed lyrics. These copies, presumably the author's own, occasionally carry his holograph corrections. A few odd items of published material follow at the end of the collection. (For a larger selection of the author's articles, see the scrapbook pages in box 4.)
Arrangement of the Collection
Correspondence is arranged chronologically; undated items are at the end, arranged alphabetically by correspondent. Manuscripts submitted to magazines edited by O'Donnell are arranged alphabetically by author. Memorabilia is arranged alphabetically by type. Notebooks are in no particular order, being undated. Scrapbooks are in alphabetical order by subject matter. Writings are arranged alphabetically by type and within that alphabetically by title.
Subject and Genre Headings
Literature -- American Fiction; Literature -- American Poetry; Literature -- Children's; New York State; Aiken, Conrad, 1889-1973.; Anderson, C. W. (Clarence William), 1891-1971.; Atwater, Richard.; Barrows, Marjorie.; Bedford-Jones, H. (Henry), 1887-1949.; Bodenheim, Maxwell, 1893-1954.; Colum, Padraic, 1881-1972.; Corey, Albert B. (Albert Bickmore); Croy, Homer, 1883-1965.; Earp, James W.; Edmonds, Walter Dumaux, 1903-; O'Donnell, Thomas C. (Thomas Clay), 1881-1962.; Starrett, Vincent, 1886-1974.; American literature -- 20th century.; Authors, American.; Folklore -- New York (State); Periodical editors -- United States.; Articles.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Notebooks.; Photographs.; Poems.; Scrapbooks.; Scripts (documents); Authors.; Editors.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mrs. Kathleen O'Donnell Springer, 1964-1968.
Inventory
- Biographical material
  - Clippings about Thomas C. O'Donnell, various dates (Box 1)
  - Obituary notices, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Sketch entitled "Thomas C. O'Donnell" by Thomas F. O'Donnell, North Country Life, Fall 1954 (Box 1)
- Correspondence
  - [General], 1900; 1915-1962; 19 folders (Box 1)
  - Undated, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - No year (Box 1)
- Manuscripts submitted to magazines edited by O'Donnell
  - Aiken, Conrad / 3 poems (Box 1)
    "Clear Evening," 1 p., typescript, undated
    "The Old House," 1 p., typescript, undated
    "Red Petals," 1 p., typescript, undated
  - Keyser, Cassius Jackson / "How To Think Mathematically", undated; 10 pp., holograph (Box 1)
- Memorabilia
  - Advertisements, undated; mostly for O'Donnell's books and Cartoons magazine (Box 2)
  - Clippings (Box 2)
  - Copyright certificates, 1943-1949 (Box 2)
  - Family mementos, 1894; 1956-1958 (Box 2)
  - Literary mementos
    - Broadside of Edwin Markham's poem "Lincoln, the Man of the People," inscribed to T. C. O'Donnell, Sept. 1928 (Box 2)
    - Broadside of Edwin Markham's poem "The Man with the Hoe," inscribed to O'Donnell, Sept. 1928 (Box 2)
    - Edwin Markham's poem "Our Israfel" (New York, Eugene R. Trott Co., 1925), with holograph corrections by the author, inscribed to O'Donnell, Sept. 1928 (Box 2)
  - Masonic pin and medal (Box 2)
  - Photographs (Box 2)
  - Portrait sketches, 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Portrait sketches, oversize (Oversize 1)
  - Reviews of books by O'Donnell, 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Miscellanea, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Miscellanea, 3 folders (Box 3)
- Notebooks
  - Nos. 1-2, undated (Box 3)
  - Nos. 3-4, undated (Box 3)
  - Number 5, undated (Box 3)
- Scrapbooks
  - General, 6 folders (Box 3)
  - General (Box 4)
  - Masonic scrapbook, 1929-1947 (Box 4)
  - Writings of T. C. O'Donnell as arranged in scrapbooks
    - Articles, general, arranged by title, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Articles for Cartoons magazine, arranged by title, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - Editorials (Box 4)
    - Plays (Box 4)
- Writings in manuscript
  - Books
    - Birth of a River
      - Research notes, 3 folders (Box 4)
      - Miscellaneous material (Box 4)
    - A Jazz History of the United States, undated; typescript (Box 5)
    - Untitled autobiographical work, undated; annotated typescript; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Essays
    - "My Bridge" and "On Coming Home", circa 1912; undated; annotated typescripts (Box 5)
  - Lectures
    - "The Black River Story", 1952 (Box 5)
    - "Folklore and History", 1949 (Box 5)
    - "Folklore of the Black River Valley", circa 1950 (Box 5)
    - "Outline of a New Approach to the Morgan Mystery", 1937 (Box 5)
  - Music lyrics
    - Miscellaneous, various dates (Box 5)
  - Plays
    - Typescripts, assorted, 5 folders (Box 5)
      "Christmas at Santa Claus's," typescript, undated
      "David Meets Goliath," typescript, undated
      "Grandpa Maypole," annotated typescript copy, undated
      "In the Treesical Woods," annotated typescript, undated
      "Jack in the Pulpit's Green Suit," annotated typescript, undated
      "Just as Thankful...!" annotated typescript, undated
      "Just the Biggest Apple...!" annotated typescript, undated
      "The Ladder of Rickety Rungs," annotated typescript copy, 1921
      "The Last Beanstalk," annotated typescript, undated
      "Little Boy Blue Bird," annotated typescript, undated
      "A Magic Journey," annotated typescript, 1923
      "The Moon Tree," annotated typescript, undated
      "Pumpkin Peter's Hallowe'en, " annotated typescript, undated and typescript copy, undated (2 copies)
      "Santa's False Whiskers," typescript, undated
      "Santa's Magic Beard," annotated typescript copy, undated
      "Solomon's Dream," typescript, undated
      "Table-Topsy Dollies," annotated typescript, undated and annotated typescript copy, undated (2 copies)
      Fragments
  - Stories
    - "How the Spoon Came Back", undated; annotated typescript (Box 5)
    - "Jimmy and the Sky Pirates", undated; annotated typescript (Box 5)
    - "The Odyssey", 1956; annotated typescript (Box 5)
    - "Spoolikins in Dollipop Land", undated; annotated typescript (Box 5)
    - "Wooly Lamb in Dollikin Land", undated; annotated typescript (Box 5)
  - Verse
    - Arranged by title, A-Z, 6 folders (Box 5)
    - Untitled and multiple poems (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous writings
    - Gags from the "On the Satiring Line" feature in Cartoons magazine, undated (Box 5)
- Writings, published
  - Articles by O'Donnell (Box 6)
  - Books and plays by O'Donnell (Box 6)
  - Contributions to anthologies (Box 7)
  - Masonic writings (Box 7)
  - Poetry and verse (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous items (Box 7)
Selected index to correspondence - Names
Adkins, Leon M. Jr. Sep 12, 1958 (to) Apr 23, 1963 (to) Sep 10, 1965 (from) Sep 17, 1965 (to) Oct 21, 1965 (to) Mar 21, 1966 (from)
Allen, James E. Jr. Jun 28, 1963 (to) Jul 3, 1963 (from) Jan 17, 1964 (to) Oct 2, 1964 (to) Feb 28, 1966 (from) Jun 27, 1966 (to) Jul 12, 1966 (from)
Armbruster, Christian H. Apr 4, 1966 (to)
Associated Executive Committee of Friends on Indian Affairs May 26, 1960 (from) Jun 13, 1960 (to) Jun 16, 1960 (from)
Associated Industries of New York State, Inc. Jul 8, 1960 (from) Jul 12, 1960 (to) Jul 29, 1960 (from) Aug 3, 1960 (to)
Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc. Mar 1, 1966 (from)
Bachman, C. Charles Mar 11, 1957 (from) Mar 16, 1957 (to) Mar 22, 1957 (to) Mar 26, 1957 (from) Apr 1, 1957 (to)
Biederstedt, F.H. Nov 15, 1960 (to)
Bodo, John Mar 10, 1966 (from) Mar 17, 1966 (to)
Bordley, James III Mar 9, 1963 (from) Mar 21, 1963 (to)
Brade, Madeleine Jan 13, 1956 (to)
Bronston, Jack E. Feb 9, 1965 (from)
Brossman, Donald G. Jul 21, 1966 (from) Jul 22, 1966 (to) Jul 27, 1966 (to) Sep 8, 1966 (from) Sep 13, 1966 (to)
Brydges, Earl W. Mar 28, 1966 (to)
Burke, Rev. Carl F. Jan 8, 1965 (from) Jan 25, 1965 (from) Jan 28, 1965 (to)
Butler, Rix Pierce Apr 26, 1967 (from) May 1, 1967 (to) May 5, 1967 (from) May 8, 1967 (to)
Carothers, J. Edward Dec 10, 1959 (to) Dec 23, 1959 (from)
Cederberg, George S. Mar 12, 1963 (from) Mar 20, 1963 (to)
Chinn, Harvey N. Mar 14, 1966 (from) Mar 21, 1966 (to) Aug 1, 1966 (from) Aug 5, 1966 (to)
Clark, Stephen C. Jan 26, 1953 (from) Jan 30, 1953 (to) Dec 26, 1953 (to) Jan 15, 1954 (from) Jan 20, 1954 (to) Jan 26, 1954 (from)
Cox, David F. Jun 30, 1966 (from) Jul 5, 1966 (to)
Corbin, Sol Neil Jan 10, 1965 (to) Apr 09, 1965 (to) Apr 15, 1965 (to) May 25, 1965 (to) May 28, 1965 (to) Jun 7 1965 (to) Jun 12, 1965 (to) Jun 17, 1965 (to) Jun 23, 1965 (to) Jul 07, 1965 (to)
Dahlberg, Edwin T. Jul 15, 1959 (from) Jul 17, 1959 (to) Jul 24, 1959 (from) May 28, 1962 (to) Jun 5, 1962 (from) Jun 8, 1962 (to) Jun 12, 1962 (from) Jan 18, 1963 (to) Jan 28, 1963 (from) Feb 4, 1963 (to)
Davie, J. Ralph Oct 28, 1954 (from) Nov 1, 1954 (to) Jun 14, 1956 (from) Oct 29, 1956 (from) Oct 31, 1956 (to) Nov 30, 1956 (from) Dec 5, 1956 (to) Dec 26, 1956 (from) Jan 7, 1957 (to) Jan 18, 1957 (from) Jan 22, 1957 (to) Mar 8, 1958 (from) Mar 14, 1958 (to) Mar 25, 1958 (to) Mar 20, 1958 (from) Aug 8, 1958 (from) Aug 12, 1958 (to)
Debevoise, Eli Whitney Nov 30, 1959 (to) Dec 17, 1959 (from) Dec 21, 1959 (to) Aug 24, 1967 (to)
Dick, James M. Sep 21, 1967 (from) Sep 26, 1967 (to)
Dirks, Howard M. Mar 30, 1956 (to) Apr 3, 1956 (from) Sep 26, 1955 (from)
Douglass, Robert R. Apr 4, 1966 (to) Apr 6, 1966 (to) Apr 22, 1966 (to) May 2, 1966 (to) May 5, 1966 (to) Jun 6, 1966 (to) Jun 13, 1966 (to) Jun 28, 1966 (to)
East Harlem Protestant Parish Dec 5, 1960 (from)
Edgar, Richard P. Dec 20, 1965 (from) Mar 7, 1966 (from) Mar 11, 1966 (to) Dec 20, 1966 (from) Dec 29, 1966 (to) Jan 10, 1967 (from)
Farley, James A. Jul 5, 1966 (to) Jul 22, 1966 (to) Jul 27, 1966 (to) Aug 2, 1966 (to) Aug 12, 1966 (to) Aug 26, 1966 (to)
Flick, Hugh C. Nov 15, 1960 (to)
Fowell, Myron W. Feb 18, 1966 (from) Mar 8, 1966 (to)
Gatland, Franklin, Z. Apr 5, 1965 (from) Apr 12, 1965 (to)
Gemmer, Robert May 19, 1966 (from) May 27, 1966 (to) May 31, 1966 (from) Jun 8, 1966 (to)
Gordon, Harold Sep 23, 1958 (from) Jun 28, 1963 (to) Aug 1, 1963 (to) Aug 2, 1963 (from)
Greenberg, Lester Jun 23, 1966 (from) Jun 27, 1966 (to)
Hale, John P. Sep 14, 1966 (from) Sep 19, 1966 (to)
Harrington, Donald Szantho Apr 12, 1967 (from) Jul 5, 1967 (from) Jul 17, 1967 (to)
Hecht, Burton Apr 5, 1965 (from)
Hesson, Samuel M. Jul 25, 1967 (to)
Hodges, Graham R. Nov 15, 1960 (to) May 8, 1967 (from) May 15, 1967 (to) Aug 10, 1967 (from) Aug 14, 1967 (to)
Holland, Hugh P. Apr 10, 1965 (from) Apr 15, 1965 (to)
Holt, Lawrence J. Jan 16, 1964 (to) Feb 4, 1966 (from) Feb 7, 1966 (to) May 26, 1966 (from) Jul 27, 1966 (from) Aug 2, 1966 (to) Sep 7, 1966 (from) Mar 27, 1967 (to) Sep 13, 1967 (to)
The Home Advisory Council of New York, Inc. Feb 2, 1956 (from)
Houck, Rodney E. Nov 4, 1965 (to)
Howe, Lee A. Jr. Jan 27, 1960 (from) Jun 7, 1960 (from) Jun 10, 1960 (to) Nov 14, 1960 (from) Nov 18, 1960 (to) Nov 23, 1960 (from) Dec 2, 1960 (to) Nov 22, 1961 (to)
Hughes, John H. Aug 14, 1964 (from) Aug 25, 1964 (to)
Hunter, William H. May 2, 1966 (from) May 5, 1966 (to)
Hurley, Thomas F. May 22, 1953 (from) Jul 16, 1953 (to) Jul 22, 1953 (to) Aug 13, 1953 (to) Aug 14, 1953 (from) Nov 12, 1953 (to)
Isham, Howard E. Jun 2, 1958 (to) Aug 18, 1958 (to)
Javits, Sen. Jacob K. Jul 26, 1960 (from)
Johnson, Douglas Dec 31, 1958 (from)
Joint Legislative Committee to Study the Publication and Dissemination of Offensive and Obscene Material Oct 8, 1965 (to)
Keating, Sen. Kenneth B. Jun 29, 1960 (from)
Kelly, H. Hugh May 15, 1967 (from) May 16, 1967 (to)
Kennedy, Sen. Robert F. Jul 30, 1966 (to) Aug 16, 1966 (repro. of letter to A. Milain Smith, Lottery-Comm. of 100,000 Against the Lottery) Oct 13, 1966 (from)
King, Martin Luther, Jr. Sep 3, 1963 (to) Oct 6, 1963 (from) Oct 11, 1963 (to) Sep 14, 1964 (to) Sep 17, 1964 (from) Sep 29, 1964 (to)
Lamb, Charles F. Jan 16, 1964 (from) Feb 6, 1964 (to) Feb 19, 1964 (from) Feb 28, 1964 (to)
Lassoe, John V.P., Jr. Mar 3, 1965 (from) Mar 10, 1965 (from) May 24, 1965 (from) Jun 1, 1965 (to) Jun 4, 1965 (from) Jun 10, 1965 (from) Jun 15, 1965 (to) Jun 21, 1965 (from) Jul 6, 1965 (to) Sep 14, 1965 (to) Oct 1, 1965 (to) Oct 13, 1965 (to) Oct 25, 1965 (from) Oct 29, 1965 (to) Jan 5, 1966 (from) Aug 18, 1966 (from) Aug 23, 1966 (to) Dec 29, 1966 (from) Apr 25, 1967 (from) May 1, 1967 (to) Aug 30, 1967 (from)
Levitt, Arthur Dec 29, 1964 (from) Jan 4, 1965 (to)
Little, M.V. Jan 4, 1961 (from) Jan 9, 1961 (to) Dec 22, 1961 (from)
Lombardi, Tarky, Jr. Feb 14, 1966 (from) Feb 17, 1966 (to)
MacMackin, Stuart Jun 9, 1959 (from) Nov 24, 1959 (to) Dec 4, 1959 (from) Dec 9, 1959 (to) May 13, 1960 (to) Oct 23, 1961 (from) Mar 23, 1964 (from) Apr 7, 1964 (to) Jun 22, 1965 (from) Oct 13, 1965 (to) May 6, 1966 (from) May 13, 1966 (to) Dec 19, 1969 (from)
Mahoney, Francis J. Nov 24, 1959 (to) Jan 18, 1960 (to) Nov 15, 1960 (to) Dec 7, 1960 (from) Dec 12, 1960 (to) Dec 23, 1965 (from) Dec 31, 1965 (to)
Mahoney, Walter J. Dec 4, 1963 (to) Dec 11, 1963 (from) Dec 18, 1963 (to) Jul 22, 1966 (to) Jul 26, 1966 (from) Jul 29, 1966 (to)
Marshall, Thurgood Oct 29, 1964 (to) Nov 12, 1964 (from)
Martin, Rev. J. Dean Mar 12, 1963 (from) Mar 21, 1963 (to)
Metcalf, George R. Dec 20, 1958 (from) Feb 19, 1965 (to) Nov 14, 1966 (from) Nov 28, 1966 (to)
Mielke, Arthur Apr 9, 1965 (to) Apr 9, 1965 (from) Nov 22, 1966 (from) Nov 22, 1966 (to) Nov 29, 1966 (to) May 10, 1967 (to) May 12, 1967 (from)
Modisher, Donald E. Feb 6, 1967 (from) Feb 21, 1967 (to)
Moore, Frank Jul 14, 1966 (to) Jul 30, 1966 (to) Aug 3, 1966 (from) Aug 8, 1966 (to) Sep 1, 1966 (to) Sep 8, 1966 (to) Sep 12, 1966 (from) Sep 15, 1966 (to)
Moore, James A.G. Dec 10, 1959 (to) Feb 28, 1967 (from) Mar 21, 1967 (from) Mar 27, 1967 (to) May 10, 1967 (from) Oct 14, 1967 (from) Dec 1, 1967 (from)
Moore, Robert E. Dec 29, 1960 (from) Jan 4, 1961 (to) Jan 10, 1961 (from)
Murphy, George A. Jan 9, 1965 (from) Jan 25, 1965 (to) Mar 12, 1966 (from) Mar 21, 1966 (to)
National Council of Churches Jan 29, 1963 (to) Sep 22, 1965 (from) Sep 29, 1965 (to)
Nevin, Hugh G. Jr. Jan 21, 1965 (from) Jan 28, 1965 (to)
New York Farm Bureau Aug 2, 1963 (from) Aug 9, 1963 (to)
New York State Dept. of State, Division of Corporations Apr 8, 1954 (to) Apr 12, 1954 (from)
New York State Congress of Parents & Teachers 1966 Jun 13, 1966 (from) Jun 27, 1966 (to)
New York State Council on Crime and Delinquency Jul 24, 1967 (from) Aug 3, 1967 (to) Aug 6, 1967 (from)
New York State Grange Aug 4, 1963 (from) Aug 9, 1963 (to)
New York Temperance Civic League, Inc. Jun 19, 1963 (from) Nov 20, 1963 (from) Aug 26, 1965 (from) Aug 30, 1965 (to)
New York State Youth Commission Dec 1, 1958 (to) Dec 8, 1958 (from) Dec 11, 1958 (to) Dec 17, 1958 (from) Dec 23, 1958 (to) Dec 31, 1958 (to)
Nickles, Earle Mar 11, 1963 (from) Mar 20, 1963 (to)
Nixon, Allan May 2, 1967 (to)
Norton, F. Paul Sep 8, 1966 (from) Sep 12, 1966 (from) Sep 15, 1966 (to) Sep 28, 1966 (from)
Peabody, Rt. Rev. Malcolm Feb 7, 1955 (to) Dec 31, 1956 (from) Jan 9, 1957 (to) Dec 22, 1958 (from) Dec 14, 1959 (to)
Peters, Robert F.R. Jun 22, 1966 (from) Jun 27, 1966 (to)